mwallpapers.com 2019-09-01

# None

This Privacy Statement discloses the way in which mwallpapers.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users. This privacy policy applies to the mwallpapers.com website ("Site") and all products and services offered by the Site. If we change our privacy policy, we will publish the modified policy and the last modified date in this page. This policy was last modified on 1 April, 2017.

## What information we collect

We have several areas where members/users can submit information to us. We also collects information automatically from our members and other users. We collect information from you when you submit photos, articles, subscribe to our newsletter or making a comment. We may run surveys, Contests or Sweepstakes in our site. We asks your Name & email address and may collect your IP address during that process. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We may also collect non-personal identification information about Users such as browsers used, operating system, Internet service providers and some technical information. 

## Cookies

We don't use Cookies our self. But the ads appearing in our website is provided by 3rd parties, who may set cookies. Ad servers are using these cookies to recognize your PC each time and to provide targeted advertisements of your interest. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Most of the ads in this website is served by Google. Google's DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may check the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/. 

## Usage of your information

We do not sell, trade, or transfer your personal information to third parties. Information is stored in a secured store area which are accessible only by authorized persons. But the information may be provided to trusted third parties (as long as they keep this information confidential) which is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We collects personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit and users can always refuse to submit any kind of user information. Personal information of the users will be published only as per request from the user (Ex: Request to publish the Biography)

## Third party links or Offers

We may put third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. But we welcome your feedback about these sites and we may remove these links if we found they are violating the policies.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

If you are a minor under 13, you are prohibited from submitting any personal information to us. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act).

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your acceptance of this policy

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. For any kind of queries or complaints, please write to us at mwallpapersteam@gmail.com
